Guide to the Beverly Lowry Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
Beverly Lowry Accessions
1957-2016
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Lowry, Beverly
UPWC.04109
54.25 Linear Feet
57 boxes Map, audio, digital files
Materials pertaining to Beverly Lowry's writing career. Items included are: manuscripts, galleys, subject interviews, reviews, notes, research material, photographs, correspondence, newspaper clippings, books, magazines, journals, and scrapbooks
Conditions Governing Access
Bulk of the collection is open for research. Materials in Series 2008-024, Box 1013 Files 1-13 are restricted as per author/donor. Restrictions may apply to some materials in Series 2016-070.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Beverly Lowry, 2002
Biographical / Historical
Beverly Lowry was born August 10, 1938, in Memphis, Tennessee, and moved with her family at age six to Greenville, Mississippi. She attended the University of Mississippi (1956-58) and graduated with a B.A. from Memphis State University in 1960. She married Glenn Lowry in June 1960, and moved with him to Manhattan. There, she pursued acting and experimented in writing. After relocating to Houston in 1965, and sending the younger of her two sons to nursery school Lowry began to write stories, some of which blossomed into novels. Lowry began teaching fiction writing as an associate professor at the University of Houston in 1976, while also pursuing acting, and serving on boards for the Cultural Arts Council of Houston, and for Houston Festival. Her fiction writing has typically been set in Texas and Mississippi. Her first two novels, Come Back, Lolly Ray and Emma Blue were both set in Eunola, Mississippi a fictional town much like her hometown of Greenville. Her next three novels and one work of non-fiction were set in Texas, with her most recent novel, The Track of Real Desires, being again set in the fictional Eunola, Mississippi.
The Lowrys lived just outside San Marcos along the San Marcos River from 1981-1991. One of the Lowrys' two sons, Peter, died in a hit-and-run accident on the highway from San Marcos to their home in 1984. This experience and other personal losses in the early 1980s "caused a marked change in the tone of Lowry's fiction. Gone is her unqualified faith in the future; present is a new preoccupation with fate or chance, even a hint that felicity may invite disaster," (Contemporary Southern Writers, St. James Press, 1999). These themes of isolation and alienation appear in The Perfect Sonya (1987), The Track of Real Desires (1994), and clearly in Crossed Over: A Murder, A Memoir (1992). Beginning in 1989, Lowry approached and visited convicted pickaxe murderer Karla Faye Tucker, on death row in Hunstville, Texas. Crossed Over relates the story of Karla Faye Tucker as well as some of Lowry's own personal story, resulting in "far more than the usual true-crime tale. Lowry interwove the story of her own troubled son with a chilling account of Tucker's dangerously out-of-control life to achieve an understanding of the human being behind an ostensibly inhuman act; her leap of imagination and empathy enabled her, at last, to make peace with Peter's death," (Texas Monthly, Feb. 2001). Lowry moved to Los Angeles in the early 1990s, and currently teaches at George Mason University, in Virginia. She continues to write essays and non-fiction, and has been working on a biography of Madame C. J. Walker, the first African-American woman to become a self-made millionaire.
Scope and Contents
Materials pertaining to Beverly Lowry's writing career. Items included are: manuscripts, galleys, subject interviews, reviews, notes, research material, photographs, correspondence, newspaper clippings, books, magazines, journals, and scrapbooks.
Index Terms
Subjects
Investigative reporting; Fiction; True crime stories
Subjects (Persons)
Lowry, Beverly
- Accession 2016-070, 7.5 Linear Feet; 7.5 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Archival materials following the creation of Beverly Lowry's book Who Killed These Girls? Cold Case: the Yogurt Shop Murders that will be released October 11, 2016. The publication pertains to the 1991 Yogurt Shop Murders of Amy Ayers, Jennifer Harbison, Sarah Harbison, and Eliza Thomas at the "I Can't Believe It's Yogurt!" shop in Austin, Texas. Included are materials for research such as news articles from Austin American-Statesman, The Austin Chronicle and Austin News8; Austin Police Department and court documents; and manuscript drafts of the book. The folder titles preceding a colon reflect Lowry's original descriptions.
  - "The Case—'98-'99"; News clippings from Austin American-Statesman and Austin Police Department's Incident Reports, July 20, 1994-December 9, 2002 (Box 2440, Folder 1)
  - "The Case—Scott Interr. & Statement-BLOG"; Typed documents of Scott's Interrogations and Austin Police Departments' supplements on Robert Springsteen, Maurice Pierce, and Mike Scott, October 8, 1997-September, 2011 (Box 2440, Folder 2)
  - "The Case—Springsteen Interrogation & R.S. Interrogation: CD, BL Notes"; Typed Interrogation with Robert Springsteen, including notes, December 15, 1991-May 17, 2001 (Box 2440, Folder 3)
  - "The Case—Arrests and Extradition"; Articles from the Austin American-Statesman about arresting the four suspects, including profiles of suspects and victims (1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 2440, Folder 4)
  - "The Case—Arrests and Extradition"; Articles from the Austin American-Statesman about arresting the four suspects, including profiles of suspects and victims (2 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 2440, Folder 5)
  - "The Case—Dochet, Affadavils, FW Release '99-'00"; Register of Actions for State vs. Springsteen, Robert, and articles from Austin American-Statesman and Laredo Morning Times, December 11, 1999-September 23, 2009 (Box 2440, Folder 6)
  - "The Case—Bond Hearing 10/99, MP & FW"; Reporter's Report, Volume 1 of 1, for Trial Court Case No. J-12, 457, October 21, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 7)
  - "The Case—Cert. #1 11/29 Merrill, Fuentes"; Reporter's Record Volume 1 of 7 Certification Hearing about Forrest B. Welborn and Maurice E. Pierce, November 29, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 8)
  - "The Case—Cert. 1A"; Reporter's Record, Volume 1 of 7, Certification Hearing for Forrest Welborn and Maurice Pierce, including statement from Michael Scott, November 29, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 9)
  - "The Case—Cert. #2 11/30 Fuentes, Skolaut"; Volume 2 of 7, Certification Hearing in the matter of Forrest Welborn, November 30, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 10)
  - "The Case—Cert 2A"; Volume 2 of 7 for Certification Hearing in the matter of Forrest Welborn, November 30, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 11)
  - "The Case—Cert #3 12/1"; Volume 3 of 7 Certification Hearing in the matter of Maurice E. Pierce, November 29, 1999-December 1, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 12)
  - "The Case—Cert #4 12/02/99 Hardesty"; Volume 4 of 7 Certification Hearing in the matter of Maurice Pierce, November 29, 1999-December 2, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 13)
  - "The Case—Cert 5 12/3 Hardesty"; Volume 5 of 7 Certification Hearing in the matter of Maurice Pierce, November 29, 1999-December 3, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 14)
  - "The Case—Cert 6 12/8 Hardesty"; Volume 6 of 7 Certification Hearing in the matter of Maurice Pierce, November 29, 1999-December 8, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 15)
  - "The Case—Cert #6A 12/08 Abreo, Stevenson"; Volume 6 of 7 Certification Hearing in the matter of Maurice Pierce, November 29, 1999-December 8, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 16)
  - "The Case—Cert #7 12/09 Merrill Closing Ruling"; Volume 7 of 7 Certification Hearing in the matter of Maurice Pierce, November 29, 1999-December 9, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 17)
  - "The Case—Adult Certification FW & MP Meurer-Families AAS: 12/01/99- 12/10/99"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman about Pierce and Welborn possibly tried as adults, November 30, 1999-December 10, 1999 (Box 2440, Folder 18)
  - "The Trial"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman on the case and police errors and misconduct causing review of cases, 1992-1993 (Box 2440, Folder 19)
  - "The Trial—APD Scandals '89-92"; Articles by Austin American-Statesman about APD officers investigated for scandals, 1989-1992 (Box 2440, Folder 20)
  - "The Trial"; Articles by The Austin Chronicle and Austin American-Statesman on Elizabeth Watson as Austin's Chief of Police and Mala Sangre case, 1993-2001 (Box 2440, Folder 21)
  - "The Trial"; Articles from the Austin American-Statesman and The Austin Chronicle, a few on carjacking case, and one on the girls' parents suing "ICBY" company, 1993-2002 (Box 2441, Folder 1)
  - "The Trial—AAS '93-'99"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman about the Yogurt Shop Murders case and investigation, 1992-1997 (Box 2441, Folder 2)
  - "The Trial—Lynch Interview Smith & Sawyer"; Typed Interview with Judge Lynch, including article from the Austin American-Statesman about lawyers Smith & Sawyer, 2001-2010 (Box 2441, Folder 3)
  - "The Trial—March-June 2000 Pre-trials"; Reporter's Record and typed court case for Michael Scott and Robert Springsteen, including notes (Box 2441, Folder 4)
  - "The Trial"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman and typed pretrial proceedings about Scott, Springsteen, and Pierce's pre-trials (1 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 2441, Folder 5)
  - "The Trial"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman and typed pretrial proceedings for Scott, Springsteen, and Pierce's pre-trials, (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 2441, Folder 6)
  - "The Trial"; Reporter's Record for continuation of pretrial proceedings, Witness List, Opening Statement for the trial, questioning of AFD, and Lusella Jones, (1 of 2), May 2001 (Box 2441, Folder 7)
  - "The Trial"; Reporter's Record for continuation of pretrial proceedings, Witness List, Opening Statement for the trial, questioning of AFD, and Lusella Jones, (2 of 2), May 2001 (Box 2441, Folder 8)
  - "The Trial"; Questioning of Thomas Powe, Chandra Morgan, Kelly Hannah, and Robert Burns Springsteen III for Springsteen case, December 6, 1991-September 13, 2002 (Box 2441, Folder 9)
  - "The Trial"; Written Statement of Michael Scott, beginning of the defense for Springsteen's trial, and Gerald Hurst's career background and questioning, (1 of 2), May 2001 (Box 2441, Folder 10)
  - "The Trial"; Written Statement of Michael Scott, beginning of the defense for Springsteen's trial, and Gerald Hurst's career background and questioning, (2 of 2), May 2001 (Box 2441, Folder 11)
  - "The Trial—RS Trial: Media"; Articles from Texas Monthly, News8 Austin, and the Austin Chronicle, on Springsteen's trial and court decision, (1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 2441, Folder 12)
  - "The Trial—RS Trial: Media"; Articles from Texas Monthly, News8 Austin, and the Austin Chronicle, on Springsteen's trial and court decision, (2of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 2441, Folder 13)
  - "The Trial—Trial Photo Notes"; Descriptions of the crime scene photos, September 30-October 4, 2010 (Box 2441, Folder 14)
  - "The Trial—2001-3 + OC. Knee Prod. 12"; Austin American-Statesman article about Chief of Police, Stan Knee, October 13, 2002 (Box 2441, Folder 15)
  - "The Trial—MS Plea Deal AC 2001"; Article from "Naked City" on the plea deals for the four suspects, September 7, 2001 (Box 2441, Folder 16)
  - "The Trial—Pretrial"; Witness List, Reporter Records on the trials, and articles from Austin American-Statesman on the trials, (1 of 2), 2000-2002 (Box 2441, Folder 17)
  - "The Trial—Pretrial"; Reporter Records on Michael Scott Pretrial, Opening Statement for the trial, and AAS article, (2 of 2), September-June 2002 (Box 2441, Folder 18)
  - "The Trial"; Michael Scott Written Statements and Reporter's Record on the Michael Scott trial, (1 of 2), September 1999-August 2002 (Box 2441, Folder 19)
  - "The Trial"; Reporter Records for Michael Scott's trial and Chandra Morgan questioning, (2 of 2), 2002-2010 (Box 2442, Folder 1)
  - "The Trial"; Michael Scott trial, 1991-2002 (Box 2442, Folder 2)
  - "The Trial—MS 53 Jones 9/12/02"; Michael Scott trial materials, (1 of 2), September 2002 (Box 2442, Folder 3)
  - "The Trial—MS 53 Jones 9/12/02"; Michael Scott trial materials, (2 of 2), September 2002 (Box 2442, Folder 4)
  - "The Trial—Lynch"; Notes on the Michael Scott trial and for Lynch Interview, including articles on Judge Lynch, August 2002-December 2012 (Box 2442, Folder 5)
  - "The Trial"; Articles from The Austin Chronicle and Austin News8 about the Michael Scott trial, September 2001-September 2002 (Box 2442, Folder 6)
  - "BRICE 2/90 ICBY"; Articles from Texas Monthly and Austin American-Statesman about other Texas crimes, including history on "I Can't Believe It's Yogurt!", 1990-2001 (Box 2442, Folder 7)
  - "Austin-General", "02/10/90 Las Cruces"; History of Austin, Texas, and article about Bowling Alley Murders in Las Cruces, New Mexico, 2009-2010 (Box 2442, Folder 8)
  - "1975 Opening", "Northcross History"; History on the Northcross Mall, 1975-2007 (Box 2442, Folder 9)
  - "Maps-Girls to ICBY", "El Nino", "Weather 12/'91"; Google Maps, Information on crimes in Austin and Local Climatological Data, 1991-2010 (Box 2442, Folder 10)
  - "Yogurt Shop Scale Drawing Model, 2001?"; Sketches showing where the bodies laid in the shop, including article on the book Murdered Innocents, 2001-February 4, 2005 (Box 2442, Folder 11)
  - "Lost Innocence"; Two articles from News8 Austin and St. Petersburg Times about Austin, TX, losing its innocence after the Yogurt Shop Murders, September 29, 2002-December 8, 2006 (Box 2442, Folder 12)
  - "John Jones-News 8-during MS Trial 9/12/02", "Huckabay"; Article from News8 Austin about Sgt. John Jones's Dismissal, including email about Sgt. Michael Huckabay's retirement, 2002-2011 (Box 2442, Folder 13)
  - "Jones Files"; Austin, TX Police and Fire Departments' Incident Reports, including the four victims' autopsy records, 1991-1999 (Box 2442, Folder 14)
  - "Jones Files-Important"; Statements from Witnesses and Autopsy Information, 1991-2009 (Box 2442, Folder 15)
  - "12/11/96 IA- J. Jones"; Internal Affairs Investigation, I.A.D. #96-350, December 11, 1996 (Box 2442, Folder 16)
  - "Jones '93"; Memos about the Yogurt Shop Murder case, including a list of suspects, 1993 (Box 2442, Folder 17)
  - Materials on Motion to Seal Autopsy Reports and Findings, Media Releases to the Public, and articles from Texas Monthly and Austin's KVUE on Kenneth McDuff, 1991-2002 (Box 2442, Folder 18)
  - Investigations and tips on the Yogurt Shop Murders, including Incident Reports, 1992-1999 (Box 2442, Folder 19)
  - "Memos from Jones Jan/Feb/March 1992", "Jones Memos June-Aug. '92"; Memos about the progress of the case and tips on suspects (Box 2442, Folder 20)
  - "ICBY Stats 1992-1994 APD-JJ"; Cleared vs. Received Tips/Witnesses/Suspects (Box 2442, Folder 21)
  - "Memo: JonesNapier 4/6/92 Long Report", "9/21/92 JJ Recap of 12/6/91"; Memo on the Homicide Task Force Update and information on the night of the murders, April 6, 1992-September 21, 1992 (Box 2442, Folder 22)
  - "Occult-MacDuff 02-09/92"; Incident Reports on suspects, involving occult members and Kenneth MacDuff, 1992-1993 (Box 2442, Folder 23)
  - Incident Reports: Supplemental Narrative Reports on tips and suspects, including memos on ICBY tips, 1992-1993 (Box 2442, Folder 24)
  - "Fall '93 Mexicans & PTSD"; Letters from the girls' families requesting APD Homicide interrogate Mexican suspect, typed interrogation of Mexican suspect, and statement from Maurice Pierce, September 22, 1993-November 19, 1999 (Box 2443, Folder 1)
  - "Chuck Meyer"; Reports of Investigation on possible suspects, including Kenneth McDuff, 1991-2001 (Box 2443, Folder 2)
  - "AAS Ch. 8 etc."; Articles from Austin American-Statesman days after the murders of the girls, December 7, 1991-December 15, 1991 (Box 2443, Folder 3)
  - "Timelines: MISC TX Justice/Wikipedia", "Photos News8 '91-'09"; Timeline and photos of significant events of the Yogurt Shop Murders case, May 29, 2009-June 16, 2010 (Box 2443, Folder 4)
  - "General: Bios Timelines Cast of Participants News8"; Timeline of the Yogurt Shop Murders and short bios of the girls and people involved in the case, June 3, 2001-August 19, 2002 (Box 2443, Folder 5)
  - "1992 #1 Timeline Jan.-Feb."; Articles from Austin American-Statesman and the Washington Post with suspect profiles and timelines, 1991-1992 (Box 2443, Folder 6)
  - "1992 IA March-May"; Articles from The New York Times and Austin American-Statesman, one article about '48 Hours' coverage on the case, March 1992-October 1992 (Box 2443, Folder 7)
  - "Cold Case Unit Hardesty '03"; Articles from Texas District & County Attorneys Association and Austin American-Statesman on murder crimes in Austin, December 9, 2002-August 2011 (Box 2443, Folder 8)
  - "Crawford '04", "RS, MS-CCA Decision '06 '07"; Articles from The Austin Chronicle and Supreme Court Records for Crawford v. Washington, 2004 (Box 2443, Folder 9)
  - "2006 '07 '08"; Articles on the trials for the four suspects and trials on people involved in the case, 2003-2007 (Box 2443, Folder 10)
  - "6/6/07 Scott CCA Opinion"; Court of Criminal Appeals of Texas Records on reversal of the suspects' court decisions, 2006-2007 (Box 2443, Folder 11)
  - "Springsteen Appeal '06"; Summary of Transcription of Videotaped Confession of Michael Scott, 1999 (Box 2443, Folder 12)
  - "DNA-Y-STR"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman, majority about DNA found on victims, 2003-2009 (Box 2443, Folder 13)
  - "Oct. 2009 Dismissal"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman about the DNA found on the victims, 2009-2010 (Box 2443, Folder 14)
  - Articles about the charges against Robert Springsteen IV and Michael Scott dropped, 2009-2010 (Box 2443, Folder 15)
  - "Pierce"; Articles from Austin American-Statesman and Austin's News8 on Maurice Pierce, including a statement of Maurice Pierce, 1991-2010 (Box 2443, Folder 16)
  - Articles from Austin American-Statesman on the case, and articles on the DNA results and false confessions, (1 of 2), 1990-2011 (Box 2443, Folder 17)
  - Articles from Austin American-Statesman on the case, and articles on the DNA results and false confessions, (2 of 2), 1990-2011 (Box 2443, Folder 18)
  - Articles from Austin American-Statesman and the Austin Chronicle about investigation failures and Springsteen trying to get his name cleared, 2006-2016 (Box 2443, Folder 19)
  - "Notes"; Handwritten notes on the case and trials from Beverly Lowry, (1 of 2), 2001-2012 (Box 2443, Folder 20)
  - "Notes"; Handwritten notes on the case and the trials from Beverly Lowry, including notes for interviews and editor agent notes (2 of 2), 2001-2012 (Box 2444, Folder 1)
  - "Notes Etc."; Handwritten and typed notes from Lowry, including correspondence between Lowry and Detective John Jones (1 of 2), 2010-2016 (Box 2444, Folder 2)
  - "Notes Etc."; Handwritten and typed notes from Lowry, including correspondence between Lowry and Detective John Jones (2 of 2), 2010-2016 (Box 2444, Folder 3)
  - Phone numbers used for research and correspondence about publication for the book (might include active numbers), 1999-2016 (Box 2444, Folder 4)
  - Posters of Lowry speaking at The Kratz Center for Creative Writing at Goucher College, March 20 [no year] (Box 2444, Folder 5)
  - Key West Literary Seminar The Dark Side program book, including Lowry's nametag, 2014 (Box 2444, Folder 6)
  - Materials about Lowry's career and events she attended, 2011 (Box 2444, Folder 7)
  - Huizache, the Magazine of Latino Literature, 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 8)
  - Two copies of Goucher Quarterly, Vol. XCVII No. 2, Summer/Fall, 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 9)
  - Four Girls: The Murders that Changed a City Manuscript, pgs. 1-189 (1 of 3), August 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 10)
  - Four Girls: The Murders that Changed a City Manuscript, pgs. 190-346, (2 of 3), August 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 11)
  - Four Girls: The Murders that Changed a City Manuscript, pgs. 347-516, (3 of 3), August 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 12)
  - Four Girls: The Murders that Changed a City Manuscript by Lowry, (1 of 3), October 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 13)
  - Four Girls: The Murders that Changed a City Manuscript by Lowry, (2 of 3), October 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 14)
  - Four Girls: The Murders that Changed a City Manuscript by Lowry, (3 of 3), October 2012 (Box 2444, Folder 15)
  - Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript by Lowry, Spring pgs. 1-153 (1of 3), 2015 (Box 2444, Folder 16)
  - Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript by Lowry, Spring, pgs. 154-328 (2 of 3), 2015 (Box 2444, Folder 17)
  - Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript by Lowry, Spring, pgs. 328-412 (3 of 3), 2015 (Box 2444, Folder 18)
  - "Various Versions Summer, Fall 2014"; Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscripts, (1 of 3) (Box 2445, Folder 1)
  - "Various Versions Summer, Fall 2014"; Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscripts, (2 of 3) (Box 2445, Folder 2)
  - "Various Versions Summer, Fall 2014"; Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscripts, (3of 3) (Box 2445, Folder 3)
  - "Nov. 2014 WK-TG"; Annotated Dark Days, Black Nights: The Crime Manuscript (Box 2445, Folder 4)
  - Annotated Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript, pgs. 1-159 (1 of 4), January-March 2015 (Box 2445, Folder 5)
  - Annotated Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript, pgs. 160-257 (2 of 4), January-March 2015 (Box 2445, Folder 6)
  - Annotated Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript, pgs. 258-309 (3of 4), January-March 2015 (Box 2445, Folder 7)
  - Annotated Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript, pgs. 310-411 (4of 4), January-March 2015 (Box 2445, Folder 8)
  - Annotated Manuscript Drafts for the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript, 2013 (Box 2445, Folder 9)
  - Articles from Austin American-Statesman and the Austin Chronicle on Springsteen looking for compensation, May 24, 2013 (Box 2445, Folder 10)
  - Annotated Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript Draft, pgs. 430-486, undated (Box 2445, Folder 11)
  - Various Annotated Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript Drafts, undated (Box 2445, Folder 12)
  - Annotated Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript Draft, pgs. 315-375, undated (Box 2445, Folder 13)
  - Various Annotated Drafts of Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders between the pages of 1-100, 2012 (Box 2445, Folder 14)
  - Various Annotated Manuscript Drafts of Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders between pages 1-97, (1 of 3), undated (Box 2445, Folder 15)
  - Various Annotated Manuscript Drafts of Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders between pages 98-313 (2 of 3), undated (Box 2445, Folder 16)
  - Various Annotated Manuscript Drafts of Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders between pages 314-444, (3 of 3), undated (Box 2445, Folder 17)
  - Greenville High School Classes of 1955 and 1956, 2011 Reunion Book, including group photo (Box 2445, Folder 18)
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript Draft (1 of 2), Aug.-Oct. 2013 (Box 2445, Folder 19)
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Manuscript Drafts, (2 of 2), August-October 2013 (Box 2446, Folder 1)
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Drafts, pps. 1-273 (1 of 3), September 2013 (Box 2446, Folder 2)
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Drafts, pgs. 274-280 (2 of 3), September 2013 (Box 2446, Folder 3)
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Drafts, pgs. 281-386 (3 of 3), September 2013 (Box 2446, Folder 4)
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft "for D. Richards", pgs. 1-178 (1 of 3), September 2013 (Box 2446, Folder 5)
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft, "for D. Richards", pgs. 179-404 (2 of 3), September 2013 (Box 2446, Folder 6)